MONA Jiravirotekul

Email: coom | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mona-jiravirotekul-26347768 / Portfolio: https://github.com/monaesthetician | Cell: (513) 429-6322

Entry-level Web Developer

More than 10 years of experience in marketing and sales in the advertising industry. Passionate about aesthetic composition and eager to learn new information. Worked collaboratively with graphic designers and art directors as a part of a team to complete projects before the deadline. Self-motivated web developer seeking an opportunity to assist a new team to succeed.

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS3
- Java script

- M.E.R.N Stack
- GitHub
- React-Redux

- SQL
- MongoDB

Experience

April 2017- Present

Assistant Manager, Ban Thai Restaurant

Cincinnati, Ohio

- Maintain and develop the restaurant website utilizing Wix.com.
- Create restaurant's print materials including; menus; closing signs; special menu boards.
- Design and create takeout menus to maximize convenience for staff and customers.
- Produced menus by working collaboratively with printing companies and designers to assure accurate, timely, and aesthetic design.
- Oversaw graphic design of restaurant logo.
- Created tailored made beverage recipes and menus by applying the understanding of the market demand and trends.
- Develop, implement, and manage to program for computerized cash register system.
- Supervised crews to maintain the highest standards in quality service and cleanliness with a constant focus on profitability.

January 2013 - July 2014 Account Executive, Money channel

Bangkok, Thailand

- Assisting in the development of sales presentations and marketing materials.
- Developed and manage revenue-producing relationships with clients and agencies.
- Provided consultation to sales managers, sales teams, and clients.
- Provided clients with convergent selling, to package several broadcast and online products.
- Other responsibilities as assigned by manager.

June 2011 - March 2013 Retail Sales Associate, King power

Bangkok, Thailand

- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Assisting customers with finding alternative merchandise to meet needs.
- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers, and promote specific merchandise.
- Participating in company training opportunities as the company offers.

April 2004 - September 2008

Account Executive, Q Advertising

Bangkok, Thailand

- Sold print advertising to local businesses and media advertising agencies.
- Worked positively and productively with the production team and finance department to provide clients' and agencies' satisfaction.
- Worked independently and collaboratively with multiple departments (internally & externally) to ensure opportunities for revenue growth are maximized.
- Worked collaboratively with internal partners to drive revenue.
- Followed all station procedures for preparing orders, resolving billing issues, submitting regular reports regarding sales, forecasts, and competitive analysis.

.. . .

April 2001 - August 2004

Customer Service, Inspire Image

Bangkok, Thailand

- Obtained client information by answering telephone calls; interviewing clients; verifying information.
- Established policies by entering client information to their requirements.
- Informed clients by explaining procedures; answering questions; providing information.
- Maintained communication equipment by reporting technical issues.
- Maintained and improves quality results by adhering to standards; recommending improved procedures.
- Stayed up to date in the field by studying new products

Education

Kable Academy • March - June 2021

Cincinnati, Ohio

Web Development

Aveda Fredric's Institute • February 2020 - August 2021

Cincinnati, Ohio

Esthiology

Waltham Forest College • 2014-2015

London, UK

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Westminster Kingsway College • 2015-2016

London, UK

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Bachelors of arts • Sripatum University • 1995 - 1999

Bangkok, Thailand

Communication Arts, Advertising